let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "Which of the following sorting algorithms can be used to sort a random linked list with minimum time complexity?",
        answer: "D. Merge Sort",
        options: [
            "A. Insertion Sort",
            "B. Quick Sort",
            "C. Heap Sort",
            "D. Merge Sort"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "In the worst case, the number of comparisons needed to search a singly linked list of length n for a given element is ",
        answer: "D. n",
        options: [
            "A. log(2*n)",
            "B. n/2",
            "C. log(2*n) -1",
            "D. n"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Let P be a singly linked list. Let Q be the pointer to an intermediate node x in the list. What is the worst-case time complexity of the best known algorithm to delete the node Q from the list?",
        answer: "A. O(n)",
        options: [
            "A. O(n)",
            "B. O(log2 n)",
            "C. O(logn)",
            "D. O(1)"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "What is the worst case time complexity of inserting n elements into an empty linked list, if the linked list needs to be maintained in sorted order ?",
        answer: "C. Θ(n2)",
        options: [
            "A. Θ(n)",
            "B. Θ(n log n)",
            "C. Θ(n2)",
            "D. Θ(1)"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "Consider the following conditions:"+
                  "<br/>"+
        "(a)The solution must be feasible, i.e. it must satisfy all the supply and demand constraints."+
        "(b)The number of positive allocations must be equal to m1n21, where m is the number of rows and n is the number of columns."+
        "(c)All the positive allocations must be in independent positions."+
        "The initial solution of a transportation problem is said to be non-degenerate basic feasible solution if it satisfies: Codes:",
        answer: "D. (a), (b) and (c)",
        options: [
            "A. (a) and (b) only",
            "B. (a) and (c) only",
            "C. (b) and (c) only",
            "D. (a), (b) and (c)"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "Which of the following is true about linked list implementation of stack?",
        answer: "D. None of the above",
        options: [
            "A. In push operation, if new nodes are inserted at the beginning of linked list, then in pop operation, nodes must be removed from end.",
            "B. In push operation, if new nodes are inserted at the end, then in pop operation, nodes must be removed from the beginning.",
            "C. Both of the above",
            "D. None of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "Which one of the following is an application of Stack Data Structure?",
        answer: "D. All of the above",
        options: [
            "A. Managing function calls",
            "B. The stock span problem",
            "C. Arithmetic expression evaluation",
            "D. All of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "The five items: A, B, C, D, and E are pushed in a stack, one after other starting from A. The stack is popped four items and each element is inserted in a queue. The two elements are deleted from the queue and pushed back on the stack. Now one item is popped from the stack. The popped item is",
        answer: "D. D",
        options: [
            "A. A",
            "B. B",
            "C. C",
            "D. D"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "Stack A has the entries a, b, c (with a on top). Stack B is empty. An entry popped out of stack A can be printed immediately or pushed to stack B. An entry popped out of the stack B can be only be printed. In this arrangement, which of the following permutations of a, b, c are not possible?",
        answer: "C. c a b",
        options: [
            "A. b a c",
            "B. b c a",
            "C. c a b",
            "D. a b c"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "Which one of the following is an application of Queue Data Structure?",
        answer: "D. All of the above",
        options: [
            "A. When a resource is shared among multiple consumers.",
            "B. When data is transferred asynchronously between two processes",
            "C. Load Balancing",
            "D. All of the above"
        ]
    },
    // {
    //     numb: 11,
    //     question: "Consider the following statements: "+
    //     "i) First-in-first out types of computations are efficiently supported by STACKS."+
    //     "ii) Implementing LISTS on linked lists is more efficient than implementing LISTS on an array for almost all the basic LIST operations."+
    //     "iii) Implementing QUEUES on a circular array is more efficient than implementing QUEUES on a linear array with two indices."+
    //     "iv) Last-in-first-out type of computations are efficiently supported by QUEUES."+
    //     "Which of the following is correct?",
    //     answer: "C. (iii) is true",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. (ii) is true",
    //         "B. (i) and (ii) are true",
    //         "C. (iii) is true",
    //         "D. (ii) and (iv) are true"
    //     ]
    // },
];